Dean of Undergraduate Studies; Records ua520
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Morris, Robert B. Dean, Undergrad. Studies, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Leonard Lapinski Memorandums, 1970-1979 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Advisement Memorandums and Programs, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Advisement Manual, Policies and Procedures, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Enrollment Projects and University Census and Course Recommendations, 1968-1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Undergraduate Studies, 1969-1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Memoranda and Correspondence from Assistant Deans, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Advisement Memoranda, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy Manual Revisions, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- "An Examination of the "W" Grade Policy-Old and New ", 1969 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Memorandum for Faculty and Staff, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Student Census and Advising Memorandums, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- SUNYA Undergraduate Academic Policies, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Proposed Programs and Class Schedules, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- "A Working Paper of Established Undergraduate Academic Policy, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Morris Memorandums, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Correspondence with Student Association, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Memoranda on Student Academics, 1964-1985 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Academic Policy Manual, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- A Working Paper of Established Undergraduate Policy, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Dean's Memorandums, 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Space Use Presentation, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Space, Physical Facility (Campus), Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Statistics Total University at Albany, Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Student Conduct, Behavior, Rights, Freedoms, ETC, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Student Evaluations of courses and teachers(SECT), Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
- A Correlation Study Using Standardized Test Score and College course grades by Richard L. Ten Eyck, Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Summer Planning Conference, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Summer Planning Conference, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Summer Planning Conference, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Summer Planning Conference, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Summer Planning Conference, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Summer Planning Conference Speeches, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Summer Planning Conference Report(rbm), Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Task-Forces-General-Reports, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Transfer Credit, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Undergraduate Education Seminar, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- UC Code of Ethics, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- UC Programs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
- UC Workload Ratios, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
- W-Grades ENG 100, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
- W-Grades POLICY, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- "W" Grade Study, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Withdrawal Procedures/Misc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Workload Analysis(Departmental) Prepared, 1969 March 31 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Budget Base and Request Materials Fiscal Year, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- University College Budget Request, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Budget 1966-67 Fiscal Year, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Budget Summer Session, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Budget, 1967-68 Program Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Budget 1967-68 Staff Recommendations, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Budget '66-'67, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Baccalaureate Degree Program In Engineering & Applied Health, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Academic Calendar Planning Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Closed Course Problem, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Grading S/U Proposal(rbm) Bibliography Committee on Educational Policy, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Grading S/U Proposal(rbm) Bibliography Herlands, Martin E., Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Grading S/U Proposal(rbm) Bibliography Howells, Ronald F., Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Grading S/U Proposal(rbm) Bibliography Lieberman, Paul A., Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Grading S/U Proposal(rbm) Bibliography Ad Hoc Committee On Grading, Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Grading, S/U General (Jan-Dec 1971), Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Grading S/U (special students), Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Grading, General, Undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Grading: A/E or S/U (Preliminary Draft of a Proposal for Optional Grading by Semester), Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Grading--Review of S/U Committee, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Grading, S/U Policy, Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
- S/U Summer, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Grading--RBM Proposal, 1971 September (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Grading, S/U General (Jan-Dec 1970), Undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
- S/U Grading Files, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Interdisciplinary Studies, Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Public Policies Study Center(PPSC) Minutes, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Second Field, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Allen Collegiate Center 3-year Baccalaureate, Undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Programs Man&His Institutions, Undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Student Permanent Records(SPR), Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Cross-Registration, Undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy Manual, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Academic Policy Memorandum, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Memoranda and Reports, 1968-1976 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- University College Advisement Manual, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- University College, Annual Report, Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
- University College, Undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
- University College, Office of, Undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Undergraduate Studies Files, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy Manual, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy Manual, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy Manual, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy, 1973 October 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Undergraduate Academic Regulations, Drafts and Planning Material, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Administrative Attitude Survey, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Companion to the Academic Information Booklet, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- University College Attitude Survey, 1968 October (Box 10, Folder 11)